{"data":[{"question":"How about him? \" He came home ___ \"","a":"safe","b":"safely","c":"with safety","d":"with safeness","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Come: is used with adjectives like apart, undone, and unstuck...","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you do with the door? The door was painted ___.","a":"whitely","b":"white","c":"with white","d":"with white hands","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Paint something (in) blue\/red\/green etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Though she didn't feed her baby milk or foods, he could ___.","a":"feed by himself","b":"feed of himself","c":"eat by himself","d":"eat for himself","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Feed (for) sbd\n- Sbd eat ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If we hurry we can ___ there in time for the opening speech.","a":"go to","b":"get to","c":"go","d":"get","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Get somewhere = arrive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What do you have to do tomorrow? \" I have to ___ in a conference.\"","a":"join","b":"taking part","c":"attend","d":"participate","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Participate in = take part in = attend = Join : to take part in an activity or event \n- Have to + Infinitive \n- Attend something, join something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"In the stillness of the night the sound ___ very loudly.","a":"resounded","b":"sounded","c":"listened","d":"heard","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Resound: if a sound such as a musical note resounds, it continues loudly and clearly for quite a long time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Who is responsible for sending out misinformation? Most of the fault ___ with the administration.\"","a":"has laid","b":"lays","c":"is laying","d":"lies","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n- Lie: (past tense) lay--( past participle) lain--( present participle) lying, (third person singular) lies","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"At last day ___ and it began to get light.","a":"broke","b":"lighted","c":"rose","d":"lightened","answer":"1","explain":"\n- At last day (of winter\/summer...) break ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"All the people in this village have black hair. \" Yes, they all ___ each other.\"","a":"resemble as","b":"resemble with","c":"resemble","d":"resemble from","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Resemble somebody = be after somebody","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"We all survived ___.","a":"from the war","b":"during the war","c":"after the war","d":"the war","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Survive + Noun: to continue to live after an accident, war, or illness...","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}